megawebdeals.com 2004-10-13

# 

|   
---  
**Our Privacy Notice**  
We understand the importance of privacy for our customers. We appreciate your trust all information we collect will be used carefully and sensibly. This notice describes our privacy policy. By visiting this site you are accepting the practices described in this Privacy Notice.   
**What Information About Customers Do We Gather?**  
The information we learn from customers helps us personalize and continually improve your shopping experience. Here are the types of information we gather.   
  
  * **Information You Give Us:** We receive and store any information you enter on our Web site or give us in any other way. Such as First and Last name, address, Phone, Email, etc. You can choose not to provide certain information, but then you might not be able to take advantage of many of our features. We use the information that you provide for such purposes as responding to your requests, customizing future shopping for you, improving our services, and communicating with you. 
  * Our site's customer account registration form requires users to give us contact information (a valid email address), unique identifiers (a password), financial information (credit card number), and demographic information (such as a zip code). When this type of information is collected it travels through the Internet in encrypted form. This website is equipped with Secure Sockets Layer (SSL), which provides strong cryptography, to transfer all of the personal information to us. Financial and login information (password) are encrypted and stored in that form on our servers.

**What About Cookies?  **  
This website uses cookies to keep track of its members' and users' activity including tracking of your shopping cart contents. Files that we store on your computer are harmless (cookie will expire after 30 days from your last visit) and cannot damage your computer nor do we store any personal information on your hard drive.  
**Sharing the Information We Receive**  
We do not market, sell, or trade your personal information to any outside companies!   
We reserves the right to release information on Internet Users if compelled to do so by proper judicial or governmental authorities. Disclosure shall be limited to only to those that this website is compelled to disclose to. At present, all information processing occurs in the United States.  
**How Secure Is Information About Me?  **  
  
  * We work to protect the security of your information during transmission by using Secure Sockets Layer (SSL) software, which encrypts information you input.
  * We reveal only the first and last four digits of your credit card numbers when confirming an order. Of course, we transmit the entire credit card number to the appropriate credit card company during order processing. 
  * It is important for you to protect against unauthorized access to your password and to your computer. Be sure to sign off when finished using a shared computer.

**What Choices Do I Have?  **  
As discussed above, you can always choose not to provide information, even though it might be needed to make a purchase or to take advantage of other services this website has to offer.   
**Children**  
We do not sell products for purchase by children. We sell children's products for purchase by adults only. If you are under 18, you may use this website only with involvement of a parent or guardian.   
**Conditions of Use, Notices, and Revisions  **  
We may find it necessary or be legally obligated to update this Privacy Policy from time to time. Any changes will be posted at this site. Except as otherwise required by law, modifications to this Privacy Policy will not affect the privacy of data collected by this website prior to the effective date of the policy change.  
**Automatic Information**  
Examples of the information we collect and analyze include the Internet protocol (IP) address used to connect your computer to the Internet; login; e-mail address; password; computer and connection information such as browser type and version, operating system, and platform as well as purchase history   
**Legal Disclaimer**  
This Site operates AS-IS and AS-AVAILABLE, without liability of any kind. We are not responsible for events beyond our direct control.  
**Contact**  
All questions regarding this privacy policy should be directed to [ps@getestore.com](mailto:ps@getestore.com)
